Yeah, sir. Uh Kobe, welcome to
Indianapolis. Um what was your reaction
to the trade and just digesting a change
of scenery?
>> Uh what's [clears throat] good uh James?
Um no, but uh when it happened, I was
shocked. Uh you know, I was going down
to uh one of my uh old teammates bullets
his community day. Um and I was driving
down and then like I got a text um from
uh from Goody. He was like called me and
then he called I called him. He was
like, "Hey, you know, this one calls I
don't like to make." And then yeah, he
said, "We traded you to the Colts." And
I was shocked. Um but but like after
like having time to think over, I was
like, "Okay, this is good." Um and yeah,
so I was shocked at first to test the
overall question though.
Joel,
>> is it is it like a feeling of being
shocked just because it felt like you
you'd established yourself in a very
clear role there, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. That Yeah. I I definitely
felt I was like, you know, you never
want to feel you don't I would never say
you feel safe, but I definitely felt,
you know, like I had, you know, been all
right, decent. Um, so but no, uh, yeah,
after talking it over my agent and like,
you know, the different ways, you know,
last year I played out of position a
little bit. I was, obviously I wasn't a
nose, but, you know, I was the nose, but
that's not my normal position. So, um,
so for me to be, you know, for coach to
come get me, it kind of let told me
that, hey, I'm going to be playing in a
a better scheme, a scheme that fits me
better. Um, and yeah, I'll be doing
something that yeah, I get to do. I get
to actually um, know how to do, I guess.
>> Nathan,
>> hey there, Colby. Um, I guess kind of on
that same line of things, h like how do
you come away from this? Are you just
more motivated um, knowing that, you
know, a team traded your way? Is it just
kind of having like a breath of fresh
air in this new situation? How do you
come away from these last five days or
so?
>> Yeah. So, I'm not going to lie, I'm
excited. Um, especially after the visit
yesterday. Um, I'm excited. Um, it's
more like I'm looking at it as a new
chapter. Like, uh, I forever be grateful
to Green Bay for, you know, drafting me,
giving me my opportunity. Um, but I look
at it like this is God's plan. He He's
ordered my steps. Um, and this is just
his next part of the journey for me. So,
yeah, that's how I'm looking at it. I'm
looking at it like it's a new, you know,
new start. Let's go. So,
>> Stephen,
>> hey Colobby, uh, you mentioned a little
bit ago that you played nose last year.
Uh, do you do you kind of have an idea
of what you might do here? Will it be
less of a a zero and more of a three or
something or do you know?
>> Uh, I mean, I I won't be playing those,
I don't think. Um, but uh I feel like,
you know, talking to them, I'm I'm going
be playing that three, a little bit of
that four, uh, anywhere three to five,
that that that three to five technique.
Um, which
>> I love. Um, you know, that's why I came
out of college playing. Been playing
most of my life. So, you know, kind of
getting me back to um, playing ball and
getting off the ball, attacking more
rather than, you know, playing that zero
squad and Yeah. So,
>> do you feel like uh affecting the
quarterback is is part of your game? Do
you feel like that's something that you
a skill set you have?
>> For sure. For sure. But like, you know,
you want to be a team player and do what
the team needs you to do. But, you know,
now you know it's time to to show what I
can do is go. Why not do it? So, yeah.
That's why I said when I when he asked
me how I felt about the trade, like I'm
I'm excited. I'm excited I get
opportunity to play ball like to truly
play ball. So, I'm excited.
>> We'll do a few more questions. Chap.
>> Yeah. Colby, if the shock has worn off,
have have you had a chance to kind of
look at the personnel you're joining and
a chance to to work with Buck? I mean,
who's probably one of the better threes
in the league.
>> Yeah, I Yeah, hell yeah. I'm not gonna
lie. When it happened, I was like, "Oh,
sh Hey, I'm going with some guys." So,
so I that kind of like, oh, all right,
that like I looked at it like I'm going
join with them. I'm going team up, you
know, I'm going to their team, you feel
me, to help them. So, it's it's always
great to to go be around the great ones
and pick their brains, learn. Um, I I'm
a big believer in that you can never
stop learning. I love to ask questions.
What you saw here, what you see here.
Um, so yeah, I looked that's the first
thing I looked at. I, you know, I buck
uh Grove, you know, you got Lu and JT.
So, you know, I I I I kind of knew what
I was coming to. So, that's why another
reason why I was excited. So, yeah,
>> appreciate it. Thank you.
>> And [clears throat] last question, Joel.
>> What do you think you can take from
playing nose last year and having some
success in Green Bay now that you're
back at a more natural position?
Um, I feel like I can take
um I mean just position flexibility. Um,
you know, stuff happens in games where
you may have to slide one way or another
and you may get caught in a position
that you're not normally playing. So,
for me, having position flexibility and
playing [sighs and gasps]
every everything from zero all the way
up out to five, like I feel like that's
a a great tool to be have, a great tool
to have. Um, and yeah, I feel like you
can just take what you've learned each
season and apply it as you keep going
and keep, you know, growing and and
playing ball.
>> Well, actually take one more, James.
>> Yeah, sorry I pump faked you there, but
um, Kobe, going into a contract year,
does that add any level of urgency?
Obviously, you play with a certain level
of that regardless, but how do you feel
about that with the change of scenery?
>> Like, I can't I'm I can't worry about
that. Like I obviously it's on my Yes,
it's I'd be lying to you if I said yeah
it's not on my mind. Yes, it's on my
mind. But at the same time, bro, you
just got to play ball, man. Like you
play ball, you have fun playing ball,
the rest take care of itself. Like I
said, this is God's plan. So whatever he
wants to happen is going to happen. Like
whether I want it or not. So um yeah,
I'm just I'm going here trying to work
and get better, bro. That's all you can
do. Um, and like I said, you do that,
everything will take care of itself.